（計(けい)）あっ…
（山田(やまだ)・吉岡(よしおか)）アア… アア…
（山田）ウワッ…
Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
ウワーッ！
First I'll run dat
（吉岡）オリャー！
（発射音）
Run around and shoot them
Brand new sound, yes still survival
Here comes the sound boy, live in this world
Intelligence, strength, and luck are swirling, flow
（山田）ウワーッ！
My swelled mind is candid
One punch to Banner in Savannah
An easy knockout, bam bam bam
One time for your mind, live through this
ウワーッ！
Around the world
It haunts me, the pain of the past
Around the noble god are borrowed things
When the seed that's sown flowers, whose is it
Live and fire the arrow of faith, more more more
There is no peace where you're going
Come on, stand up, don't give up the fight
Now, yes, this instant, die die die
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
（加藤(かとう)・計）あっ…
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
（銃声）
（ネギ星人：親）アッ…
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
（吉岡）ウワーッ！ ウワーッ！
（銃声）
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Kei, You're Awesome!
（計）マ… マジかよ
I don't believe it.
（岸本(きしもと)）加藤君…
Kato...
Make it stop. Make it stop...
（加藤）もうイヤだ　もうイヤだ…
冗談じゃねえ… 冗談じゃねえぞ
This isn't funny.
This is NOT funny!
…だよな　普通 逃げたいよな
Damn straight, most people would run away.
あ… あんたの…
I...
あんたの気持ちは分かる　だから…
I understand how you feel, so...
何言ってんだよ！ 逃げろって！
What are you talking about? Get out of there!
（ネギ星人：親）ズゴヌアバ！
ジオニバッグ…
アア～ッ！ アア～ッ！
俺は… こ… 殺し合ったりとか
I don't want to kill anybody.
そういうの したくない
マガ… マヌガ！ ズマ！ ズマ！
You don't understand what I'm saying. Damn!
（加藤）
伝わんねえよな　ちくしょう…
お… 俺だって―
I wanted to save your buddy! I swear!
あんたの仲間 助けたかった
俺だって！
（ネギ星人：親）
ヴーツ！ ヴーツ！ ズマ！
（計）何言ってんだ？ あいつ
What the hell is he talking about?
Damn! This... This doesn't make sense.
くそ… 何なんだ？ これ
ワケ分かんねえ
What am I doing? Shit!
何やってんだ 一体… 俺 くそ…
Kei, I think I'm gonna die.
計ちゃん 俺 死ぬかも…
死にたくない
くそ… どうすりゃいい？
I don't want to die.
Damn it! What should I do?
I don't wanna die. I don't wanna die.
死にたくない　死にたくない
Will this thing work?
使えるのか？
なんか あいつらのと形違うけど…
It looks different from the others.
ヴォア！ ズモァ！
Calm down! Calm down!
落ち着け 俺… 落ち着け！
（ネギ星人：親）ンンッ！
（切りつける音）
Kei, what's gonna happen to us?!
計ちゃん 俺ら どうなる？
生き残れんのか？
Will we survive?! If I shoot, will we live?!
撃つと生き残れんのか？
分かんねえよ！
分かんねえけど とにかく撃て 加藤
I don't know!
I don't know, but just shoot him, Kato!
撃つと どうなる？
撃つと帰れんのか？
What'll happen if I shoot him?!
If I shoot, will we be able to go home?
（計）だから 分かんねえって！
I said, I don't know!
Are you gonna shoot?
（岸本）撃つの？
I said, I don't know!
分かんねえって言ってんだろう！
ダメだ…
It's no use!
やっぱ ダメだ
It didn't work.
What the hell are you doing? Shoot!
何やってんだ　撃て！
じゃ あなたが撃ってよ！
（計）俺か？ 俺かよ…
Why don't you shoot him?!
Me? Why me?
早く撃って！
Shoot him! Now!
Shoot him!
撃って！
（加藤）ウワッ…
あっ… 加藤君！
Kato!
加藤君が…
Kato fell!
Shit... We're in deep shit now.
やべえ… これ マジで やべえ
Oh, shit! This is scary!
怖(こえ)え… くそ… 脇腹 痛(いて)え
My side aches!
Grab on! Hurry!
つかまれ 早く！
さっき あんたが撃っていれば…
If only you'd just shot him back there...
C'mon! You were so scared,
you were about ready to run too!
（計）お前だって
ビビって後ずさってたじゃねえか！
Kato's probably dead!
加藤君 きっと死んじゃったよ！
And that's MY fault?! Why?
俺のせいかよ？ なんでだよ！
俺 加藤を見殺しにした？
Did I leave Kato for dead?
I mean, who could possibly think
about others at a time like that?
だって あんな状況で
他人のこと考えられるヤツいるか！
That's just the way it goes!
しょうがねえだろう！
（計）腹痛え… 運動不足だ
Cramps! I'm so out of shape!
He... He's coming!
来る 来るよ！
何だよ！
なんで追われてんだよ？ 俺たち
Why? Why is he chasing us?
You should've shot him!
撃てばよかったのに！
（計）だから…
I told you...
Somebody!
誰か… 誰か警察 呼んでください！
Somebody call the cops!
（激突音）
（ネギ星人：親）アアッ！
（男性Ａ）
やっべえ… だ… 大丈夫ですか？
Oh, no! Are you all right?
はねられてやんの
（岸本）死んだ？
Did he get hit by that car?
Is he dead?
What?
（男性Ｂ）あれ？
No one's there.
（男性Ａ）誰もいないじゃん
（男性Ｂ）うん
Yeah.
（男性Ａ）行こう 行こう
（男性Ｂ）うん…
Let's get out of here.
Maybe we ran over a cat or something.
猫か何か はねたかな？
（計）
なっ… おい こら！ あんたな…
Hey, come on now!
あの…
携帯 貸してほしいんですけど
Can we borrow your cell phone?
What's wrong?
（男性Ｂ）どうした？
（男性Ａ）おい ここ 何か いる
Something's here.
（計）えっ？
（男性Ｂ）はぁ？ 何言ってんだよ
What? What are you talking about?
There's something invisible here.
（男性Ａ）透明なヤツがいる…
What's going on? Are we in Hell?
（計）
どうなってんだ？ ここって地獄？
（男性Ａ）く… 車が！
My car!
Drive Safely
So I am dead.
（計）死んでたんだ 俺
ハハッ…
やっぱ死んでたんだ　そっか…
I really AM dead.
Man...
もう俺 家(うち)にも帰れないんだ
I can never go home.
Oh, well...
まあ いっか…
I bet no one's...
俺 死んでも 悲しむヤツなんか
この世に いないしな
sad to see me go.
（岸本）いい子だったのに…
I was always a good girl.
I always tried to be a good girl.
頑張って
いい子してきたんだけどな
But if it's going to wind up like this...
こんなことになっちゃうんなら…
なんでだろう？
あいつは泣いてくれそうな気がする
I get the feeling he'd cry for me. Why is that?
Why do I think that?
なんで そう思えるんだろう？
Kei, you're so cool. You're cooler
than Goku or Kenshiro.
（少年時代の加藤）
計ちゃん まじカッコイイよ
悟空(ごくう)とかケンシロウより
（少年時代の計）はぁ？ 俺が？
Who? Me?
（少年時代の加藤）俺…
One day I'm gonna be like Kei.
絶対 いつか
計ちゃんみたいになりたいよ
See, I'm not so smart, so I go
to the school all the punks go to.
俺 頭悪いから―
よくない連中が集まる学校
行ってるんだけど そこで―
So I tried to be like you.
なんとか計ちゃんに近づこうって
頑張ってんだよね
ベガレボ キャゼ！
そうだ！
That's it!
（計）そうだ あのころの俺は…
Yeah, back then...
ズマ ズマ！ ボゲラ！
I was different.
今と違った
あのころの俺は
怖いもんなんか なかった
Back then, I wasn't afraid of anything.
あのころの俺は
状況がヤバければヤバイほど…
Back then, the bigger the mess
I was in, the better!
ハッ… 玄野(くろの)君！
Kurono!
そこを乗り切ったときの
ヒーローな俺を想像して興奮してた
I'd imagine getting myself out of it
and being a hero!
It excited me!
And then, I'd do it!
（計）
そして そのとおりになってた！
I've still got it!
いける まだ！
I can't imagine beating this guy, but...
こいつを倒す映像は浮かばないけど
逃げきってやる
I'll get away from him, no matter what!
何があろうと 必ず！
He's scary... That guy's scary!
怖え… あいつ 怖え
（計）ウワーッ！
（加藤）ハッ…
Kei?!
計ちゃん？
There he is!
（子供Ａ）いたぞ！
（子供Ａ）待て！
Wait!
A thousand yen for the one who gets Kurono!
（子供Ｂ）
玄野 捕まえたヤツ 1,000円
I wonder if he's dead?
あいつ 死んじまったのかな？
（滑る音）
ウワッ…
Stairs!
階段！
I'll jump down them!
跳んでやる！ あんときみたいに
Like I used to!
ウワ～ッ！
Awesome!
（加藤）すっげえ…
How could I jump so high?
なに こんな高く跳んでんの？
俺 跳び過ぎ？
I jumped too far!
ヤダ… 冷えちゃった
This is awful. I'm so cold.
No, I might make it out of this with
just two or three broken bones.
（計）
いや でも 骨の２～３本で済むかも
Oh, wait, I'm already dead!
…ていうか 死んだんだっけ 俺
（空気の噴射音）
ウワッ… ウワーッ！
What the hell is going on?
（計）どうなってんだ？ 一体
何が何やら もう…
I have absolutely no idea.
Kei!
（加藤）計ちゃん！
計ちゃん 逃げろ！
Kei, run!
ンンッ… ちきしょう！ 怖え！
Damn it! I'm scared!
Run!
逃げろ！ け… 計ちゃん 逃げろ！
Run, Kei!
やっぱ すげえ… 計ちゃん…
Kei, you really are awesome.
Damn it! Kato!
ちきしょう… 加藤！
（ネギ星人：親）アア～ッ！
ズマゴ… ドクッ… アアッ…
Bring it on, fucker!
来やがれ くそ野郎！
ズマゴ… グアーッ！
ズマ ズマゴ…
Just you try to crush it!
（計）くそ… つぶしてみろよ
ズマ ズマ！
（計）オラッ！
…んなろう！
（殴る音）
Bastard!
You're a fucking wuss!
弱っちいんだよ てめえ！
ちくしょう　かかってこい！
You jerk! Hey, bring it on!
ネ… ネギあげます
ネ… ネギあげます　ネギあげます
Take my green onions!
はぁ？ 何言ってんだ てめえ！
聞こえねえんだよ！
What are you saying, fucker? I can't hear you!
（ネギ星人：親）ネギあげます！
（殴る音）
Take my green onions!
Please forgive me!
許してください…
（殴る音）
許すわけねえだろう！ この…
Why should I, you bastard?
許してください…
Please forgive me!
計ちゃん…
（計）ハッ… 加藤！
Kei...
Kato!
You can stop now...
（加藤）もう やめてやってくれ…
もともと 俺らが… わる…
It was... our fault... to begin...
はぁ？ よく聞こえないって
何だよ？
I can't hear you! What did you say?
Take my green onions! Please forgive me!
（ネギ星人：親）
ネギあげます　許してください
（ネギ星人：子）
ネ… ネギあげます　ネギあげます
Take my green onions! Take my green onions!
すまない…
I'm sorry.
なに謝ってんだよ？ やめろって！
What are you apologizing for? Knock it off!
だけどさ あいつにしてみりゃ…
（計）謝ってんじゃねえよ！
But think about them!
Don't say you're sorry!
（計）あっ… お… お前
You!
お前 どこにいたんだ？
Where have you been?
（西(にし)）近くにいたよ ずっと
I was close by the whole time.
なんとか時間内か…
点数は 今回は あんたにやるよ
So we've managed to make it in time.
I'll let you have the points this time.
その銃で こいつ撃ってみろよ
Shoot him with that gun.
撃つって これで？
Shoot him with this?
Yeah, with that.
うん　それ
どうなる？ 撃つと…
（西）いいから
What'll happen if I shoot him?
Just do it.
Pull both triggers.
（西）引き金 ２つとも引いて
（計）お… おい…
Hey, if I shoot him with this gun, won't he...
まさか この銃 撃ったら…
He'll die, of course.
うん　死ぬよ もちろん
I bet you'd love to see him die, wouldn't you?
（西）
見たいでしょう？ こいつ死ぬとこ
We all start out as pure and innocent babes
Even if you taste the bitter fruit,
don't be discouraged, walk straight
I know it's in the past, but the rain still stings
I'm lonely as floating ice
I kiss your thin finger
And remember you crying
Even if this is the end
I won't forget your last kiss
I won't forget
I won't forget his kiss
（西）命を拾うためには
ほかの命を捨てねばならない
In order to save a life, you must
throw another life away.
In order to throw it away, you must kill.
捨てるためには殺さねばならない
Once you cross that line,
an unbelievable world awaits you.
一線を越えれば その先には
信じられない世界が待っている
なあ 撃っちゃえよ
So just shoot him.
Next time: "Okay, Here Are Your Scores"
次回
“それぢわ ちいてんをはじぬる”